<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Our projects on Ukrainer In Trier</title><link>https://www.ukrainer-in-trier.com/en/projects/</link><description>Recent content in Our projects on Ukrainer In Trier</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://www.ukrainer-in-trier.com/en/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Art space / art</title><link>https://www.ukrainer-in-trier.com/en/projects/art/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.ukrainer-in-trier.com/en/projects/art/</guid><description> We create exhibitions, historical props. We create and through creativity - we convey our values and feelings.</description></item><item><title>Catering/ Food courts/ Fairs</title><link>https://www.ukrainer-in-trier.com/en/projects/catering/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.ukrainer-in-trier.com/en/projects/catering/</guid><description>We convey the entire Ukrainian flavor through creativity and traditional national food Taste Ukrainian specialties: from the famous beetroot soup (borsch) to stuffed dumplings (vareninki) to delicious drinks (uzvar) and relax with Ukrainian music. We present you hand made souvenirs from Ukraine.
Best regards, the "Ukrainer in Trier" team.
With the support of: City-Initiative Trier e.V., ProIntegration e.V., Verein Hoffnung.
MENU Cooked with love Ukrainian borsch 300 ml
Vegetable broth, cabbage, beetroot, carrot, onion, garlic, pepper, potato, tomato paste, beans, spices (salt, pepper, bay leaf, sugar), celery, parsley, oil, parsnip.</description></item><item><title>Creative team "Free Birds"</title><link>https://www.ukrainer-in-trier.com/en/projects/free-birds/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.ukrainer-in-trier.com/en/projects/free-birds/</guid><description>Creative team "FREE BIRDS" The mysterious ancient Trier attracts talented people, binds and unites them. That's right, previously unknown people - were able to become a single incredible team. Music, dancing, singing, creative skills - everything is in abundance. Thanks to the union, we manage to introduce Europeans to Ukrainian culture and folklore.
Anna Stetska singer
Liza Kondratenko singer, musician
Margarita Nagorna singer
Angelina Dotsenko singer
Sofia Deriguz bandurista, singer</description></item><item><title>Educational projects</title><link>https://www.ukrainer-in-trier.com/en/projects/educational-projects/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.ukrainer-in-trier.com/en/projects/educational-projects/</guid><description> Teachers, even far from home, nurture the Ukrainian language and impart knowledge to young children. The educational project "Sunflower" is a real find for every schoolchild!</description></item><item><title>Help in Trier</title><link>https://www.ukrainer-in-trier.com/en/projects/trier-help/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.ukrainer-in-trier.com/en/projects/trier-help/</guid><description> Every Ukrainian has the opportunity to ask for help and will certainly receive it. We invite you to visit the psychological support group, which is conducted by a psychologist, coach Anna Plyusnina.</description></item><item><title>Making trench candles</title><link>https://www.ukrainer-in-trier.com/en/projects/candels/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.ukrainer-in-trier.com/en/projects/candels/</guid><description> By joining forces with the German community and German charitable organizations, we started making trench candles. Trench candles are more efficient than ordinary candles because they burn longer and give more heat.</description></item><item><title>Psychological help</title><link>https://www.ukrainer-in-trier.com/en/projects/psych-help/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.ukrainer-in-trier.com/en/projects/psych-help/</guid><description>No one deserve to experience grief, pain and despair alone. Sometimes it's just as hard for others. And it seems that there is no one to share your worries and anxieties with. Because it's bad for everyone. Because I'm afraid to get bored. Many different "Because".
But a person needs a person, the one who can withstand the storm of emotions, difficult and unpleasant.
And a psychologist can become such a person.</description></item><item><title>Ukrainian books</title><link>https://www.ukrainer-in-trier.com/en/projects/books/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.ukrainer-in-trier.com/en/projects/books/</guid><description> The Ukrainian book is the heart of the people. The project was developed within the framework of the scholarship program "NUMO. The scholarship program "Libraries and Archives for Refugees from Ukraine", financed by the Commissioner of the Federal Government for Culture and Mass Media on the basis of a resolution of the German Bundestag. Books here</description></item><item><title>Ukrainian cultural center</title><link>https://www.ukrainer-in-trier.com/en/projects/cultural/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.ukrainer-in-trier.com/en/projects/cultural/</guid><description>Ukrainian cultural center Together we create a new story and preserve the old one! + School Children should have access to the same lives as their peers in Ukraine. Many of them will return home - that's why our task is to make a minimal "gap" in knowledge. And school is a great opportunity for children to communicate with each other. + Course, seminars Use new changes as additional opportunities!</description></item><item><title>What else do we do</title><link>https://www.ukrainer-in-trier.com/en/projects/whatelse/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.ukrainer-in-trier.com/en/projects/whatelse/</guid><description> What else do we do? We try to combine all directions so that everyone who is forced to leave home feels as comfortable and protected as possible. The war goes on - but we must keep dreaming, planning and developing! Organization of rallies and promotions Master classes, seminars Sports and dance sections Organization of excursions and walks Catering and fairs Development of journalism</description></item></channel></rss>